smart contracts can doubt that something
智能合约可以通过触发来怀疑区块链上发生了什么
has happened on the blockchain by firing
events applications can be notified when
发出事件而不是发出事件时可以通知事件应用程序
an event is emitted instead of
constantly monitoring a contract on a
不断监控区块链上的合同以了解状态变化
blockchain for state changes to occur
this is like YouTube if you subscribe to
这就像YouTube，如果您订阅的频道不必重复
a channel you don't have to repeatedly
visit the channel to check if a new
前往频道查看最近是否有新影片上传
video was uploaded recently you get
notified when a new video is released in
在此视频中发布新视频时收到通知，我们将讨论如何
this video we're gonna go over how to
write and fire events using solidity and
使用牢固性编写和触发事件，我们还将介绍如何克服过去
we'll also go over how to get past
events that are already on the
区块链上已经存在的事件以及如何订阅您
blockchain and how to subscribe to you
events using a library called web pages
使用称为网页的库来定义事件，您可以从
to define an event you start with the
keyword event followed by the name of
在这种情况下，关键字事件后接事件名称，我将其称为
the event in this case I'm gonna call it
dog inside the parentheses you can pass
狗在括号内，您可以将要登录的数据传递到
the data that you want to log on to the
blockchain here I'm gonna log the sender
区块链在这里，我将使用一些消息记录交易的发送者，
of a transaction with some message and
you can also create events where no
您还可以创建未传递任何参数的事件
parameter is passed
next I'm gonna show you how to fire an
接下来，我将向您展示如何触发事件，因此首先，我需要创建您的
event so first I need to create your
function and inside the function we're
功能，在功能内部，我们将首先通过电子邮件发送蝙蝠
gonna email the bat first
okay a public function called fire
好吧，一个称为火灾事件的公共功能，您可以将事件记录到
events you can log an event onto the
blockchain by starting with the keyword
以关键字email开头，后跟事件名称的区块链
email followed by the name of the event
that you want to log in our case we're
您想登录我们的案例，我们将与Lee一起找到它的日志事件，然后
gonna find it a log event with Lee then
we're also gonna log the sender of this
我们还将使用消息hello world记录此交易的发送者
transaction with the message hello world
and you can also fire multiple events so
您还可以触发多个事件，所以在这里我将再次触发同一事件
here I'm gonna fire the same event again
with a different message followed by a
带有不同的消息，然后是另一个叫另一只狗的事件，让我们
different event called another dog let's
compile and deploy and see these events
编译并部署，并在运行中查看这些事件，执行功能触发
in action execute the function fire
events and click on the transaction mode
事件，然后单击事务日志中的事务模式以搜索
inside the transaction log search for
the keyword logs that's where you will
关键字日志，您可以在其中找到所有触发的事件
find all of the events that was fired
when this function was called in our
在本例中，当调用此函数时，您可以在此处看到
case you can see here that the
that log was fired twice followed by
该日志被触发两次，然后键入另一个日志
typing another log
furthermore you can see here that the
此外，您可以在此处看到使用参数触发了日志事件
log event was fired with the parameters
that we passed in in this case Center is
在这种情况下，我们传入的中心是交易的中心，
the center of the transaction and the
message boards hello world which is the
留言板你好世界，这是在这些日志中触发的事件
event that was fired here these logs
will be stored on the blockchain but
将存储在区块链上，但智能合约将无法访问
smart contracts won't be able to access
these logs so one use case of firing
这些日志，因此触发事件的一个用例是记录某事
events is to record that something
happened on the blockchain and it is
发生在区块链上，比在智能设备上存储数据便宜
cheaper than storing data on a smart
contract past events are all stored on
合同过去的事件都存储在区块链上，但通常情况下您不是
the blockchain but oftentimes you're not
interested in all of the events and you
对所有事件感兴趣，并且您希望能够快速搜索
want to be able to quickly search for
specific events such as searching for
特定事件，例如搜索所有发件人为
all log events where the sender is a
certain address that's where the keyword
通过使用关键字进入关键字索引的特定地址
index comes in by using the keyword
indexed on a parameter you can quickly
在参数上建立索引，您可以快速搜索该参数所在的事件
search for events where the parameter
equals a certain value for example if
等于某个值，例如，如果此事件记录在
this event was recorded on the
blockchain 100 times by different
区块链由不同的发件人进行100次，您想找到所有这些
senders and you want to find all of this
event triggered by a certain sender one
由某个发送者触发的事件的一种执行方法是获取所有日志
way to do it is to get all of the logs
and then check that the sender is equal
然后检查发件人是否等于您要查找的地址
to the address that you're looking for
but since we're using the keyword
但由于我们使用的是此处索引的关键字，所以我们要做的就是发送一个
indexed here all we have to do is send a
search query to the Italian phone asking
搜索查询到意大利电话，询问发件人相等的所有日志
for all logs where the sender is equal
to certain address in response you'll
到特定地址作为响应，您将获得发件人所在的所有日志
get all of the logs where the sender is
equal to that address that's an example
等于该地址，这是在区块链上使用智能合约的示例
using a smart contract on the blockchain
so I wrote a script in ojs to get past
所以我用ojs编写了一个脚本，以从区块链上的合同中获取过去的事件
events from a contract on the blockchain
for this script I chose a one on
为此脚本，我选择了一个合同上的骰子表硬币
contract called the dice table coin
since it's pretty active on the Italian
简而言之，它在意大利区块链上非常活跃
blockchain in short the dice table coin
is a crypto currency where the price
是一种加密货币，每个硬币和胸骨的价格保持在1美元左右
stays around $1 per coin and sternum
stable point how it maintains price
视频如何保持价格稳定以及为什么有用的一个稳定点
stability and why it's useful is a video
for another day so now let's go over the
再过一天，现在让我们先逐行浏览代码，然后导入Web
code line by line first we import web
the web tea is like a bridge between the
网络茶就像区块链和其他程序之间的桥梁
blockchain and other programming
languages it allows us to send
它允许我们发送交易并从中获取数据的语言
transactions and get data from the
blockchain using a program like
使用JavaScript和ojs之类的程序进行区块链操作，接下来我们导入
JavaScript and ojs next we import the
ABI of the dice table clone API stands
骰子表克隆API的ABI代表应用程序二进制接口ABI
for application binary interface the ABI
allows different programs to interact
允许不同的程序与
with the smart contract on the
blockchain in our case the ABI of the
在我们的案例中，区块链的骰子表硬币的ABI将使我们能够获得所有
dice table coin will allow us to get all
the events fired by a contract of the
骰子表硬币合约引发的事件我得到了ABI
dice table coin I got the ABI of the
dice table coin by going to either scan
通过扫描任一骰子表硬币，您是否通过以下方式搜索合同
are you searching for the contract by
the address and clicking on contract and
地址，然后点击合同，然后向下滚动至合同API
then scrolling down to a contract API in
order to use web 3 we need a eternian
为了使用Web 3，我们需要一个eternian电话节点，这意味着我们需要
phone node that means that we need to
run the ethereum software and download
运行以太坊软件并下载所有区块链，但我们没有
all of the blockchain but we don't have
time to download all of the blockchain
是时候下载所有区块链了，理论上这就是IO来的地方
so that's where in theory the IO comes
in by signing up to inferior dot IO it
通过注册劣等点IO，您可以快速访问意大利语
allows you to quickly access the Italian
boxing without running your own Italian
在不运行您自己的意大利语软件的情况下进行拳击，接下来我们通过以下方式初始化web 3
software next we initialize web 3 by
passing in the URL of our Italian for
传递我们意大利语节点的URL，这是合同的地址
node this is the address of the contract
of the dice table coin this is the
的骰子表硬币，这是我们将要运行的功能
function that will be run when we
execute the script inside the function
在函数中执行脚本，我们首先获取最新的块，然后我们
we first get the latest block next we
load up the contract of the dice table
使用我们复制过来的ABI加载骰子表硬币的合约
coin using the ABI that we copied over
from eater Skanda I oh and finally
食者Skanda的我哦，终于研究了转移事件
research for the transfer event that was
fired in the last 100 blocks and then
在最后100个区块中触发，然后打印出
print out the logs that
execute the script open your terminal
执行脚本，打开终端，然后输入节点
and then type in node
followed by the path of the script in
然后是脚本的路径，在这种情况下，您将位于源代码中，
this case you'll be on the source and
the filename is called get past blogs
该文件名称为获取过去的博客
once you get the response you can check
收到响应后，您可以检查事件的名称是否为
that the name of the event was
transferred and these parameters were
转移，并且这些参数与之前的事件有关
involved with the event earlier I
mentioned that the parameters of any
提到任何银行的参数都可以建立索引，以便您可以
bank can be indexed so that you can
quickly search for any bank where the
快速搜索参数等于您所需要的值的任何库
parameter equals a value that you're
looking for looking at the code for the
寻找看骰子表硬币合约的代码，您可以看到
dice table coin contract you can see
here that the transfer event uses the
在这里，转移事件使用关键字索引的参数很少
keyword index few of the parameters
since the parameter name DST is indexed
由于已为参数名称DST建立了索引，因此我们可以快速搜索事件，其中
we can quickly search for events where
DST is equal to this address from the
DST等于此地址，从响应中只会打印出DST
response will only print out the DST
parameter so that we can quickly verify
参数，以便我们可以快速验证所有DST参数
that all of the DST parameters that
return is equal to the address that we
return等于我们提供的地址，一旦获得
provided execute the script once you get
the response you can see here that all
您可以在此处看到的响应是，所有事件都包含该地址，
of the events contain that address that
we provided for the DST parameter so I
我们提供了DST参数，所以我只是向您展示了如何从中获取事件
just showed you how to get events from
the blockchain and how to filter them by
区块链以及如何使用网页通过索引参数过滤它们
index parameters using webpages next i
want to show you a demonstration of how
想要向您展示如何订阅活动的演示，所以这里是
to subscribe to events so here's the
script to subscribe to events so here's
订阅事件的脚本，因此这是订阅合同的代码，
the code to subscribe to contract and
we're going to be using the dice table
我们将再次使用骰子表硬币合约
coin contract again the top part is
mostly the same from the basket inside
初始化主功能时，篮子中的内容基本相同
the main function you initialize the
contract and subscribe to the event
签订合同并订阅事件转移，因此转移事件为
transfer so when the transfer event is
emitted this function will be called
发出此函数将在函数内部被调用（如果有箭头）
inside the function if there's an arrow
we're going to log it and I were also
我们要记录它，我也要记录被解雇的事件
gonna log the event that was fired
similar to how you can filter out past
类似于您如何过滤过去的事件
events by
experimenters you can also filter out
实验者，您还可以使用index参数过滤掉传入的事件
incoming events by using index parameter
so here we're saying that we only want
所以我们在这里说的是，我们只想听事件发生的机会，
to listen to the chance for event where
the sender is equal to this address
发送者等于此地址执行脚本并等待
execute the script and wait for
something to print out when the transfer
当发送方等于此的转移事件时要打印的东西
event where the sender is equal to this
address is recorded onto the blockchain
地址记录在区块链上，您将看到打印出来的响应
you'll see the response printed out into
the terminal here I've been running the
在这里的终端上，我已经运行了几分钟的脚本，您可以看到
script for a few minutes and you can see
that some of the logs were printed out
某些日志已打印出来，我会将这段代码上传到github上，
I'll upload this code onto github and
provide the links in the descriptions
提供以下说明中的链接，以便随时浏览
below so feel free to play around in
this video I showed you how to write
这个视频我向您展示了如何牢固地编写事件，您可以通过一些
events in solidity you can pass some
parameters into an event and three of
参数转换为事件，并且其中三个参数可以通过以下方式建立索引：
the parameters can be indexed by
indexing the parameter you'll be able to
为参数建立索引，您将能够快速过滤掉过去的事件并使用
quickly filter out past events and using
web DJ yes I showed you several demos of
网络DJ是的，我向您展示了如何演示过去的事件以及如何进行
how to get past events and how to
subscribe to incoming events that's all
订阅传入的事件，这是我在代码中获得此视频链接的全部内容
I got for this video links in the code
will be in the description below thanks
将出现在下面的说明中，感谢您的观看，下次见
for watching and I'll see you next time